(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-26T12:30:13.618256",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あぁ whipped した ケーキのような街は 好き！雪！本気マジック！
Ah, a town like a frosted cake, suki! yuki! maji magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは
Confetti given by the sky
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
is the angel's wings celebrating winter's festival.
白銀の国へ出かけられる go go go
We'll head to a country of silver snow, go go go!
雪の汽車が街を駆け choo choo choo
A snow train runs through the town, choo choo choo!
絵本みたいな景色を
Landscapes like from picture books
君に見せてあげるから
I will show them to you, so
願い込め呪文 さぁ (さぁ) 歌えて (さんはい)
Make a wish, a charm, now (now), sing along (ready, set)!
abcd ドド シシ ララ シシ マジカル ミラクル クール pop！
abcd do do shi shi la la shi shi magical miracle cool pop!
あぁ whipped した ケーキのような街は 好き！雪！本気マジック！
Ah, a town like a frosted cake, suki! yuki! maji magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは
Confetti given by the sky
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
is the angel's wings celebrating winter's festival.
light up したオーロラ色の街は 好き！雪！本気マジック！
The illuminated town of aurora, suki! yuki! maji magic!
子どもでいられたら dream land
Wish I could just be a child, dreamland.
“ladies and gentlemen, welcome to snow miku!”
ツンと冷たい季節が好き love love love
Lovin' the sharp cold weather, love love love!
アイスも魔法もとけないように ヒュールーヒュールー
Hoping ice and magic won't melt, whew whew whew!
ずっとこのままじゃダメなのかな やっぱりドキドキしたいな
Can't we be like this forever? I still wanna feel excited.
未来求め呪文 今 (なう) 歌えて (さんはい)
Imagine the future now, recite a charm (here we go)!
1234 水金地火木 マジカル ミラクル クール pop！
1234, Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, magical miracle pop!
あぁ ホップした ウサギ のような 気分 好き！雪！本気 マジック！
Ah, feelin' like a hopping rabbit, suki! yuki! maji magic!
大地がくれる元気得たら
When energy from the earth comes,
思い通り明日を生きていけるよ
we can live tomorrow just how we want to.
まぶしい白に染まるハート 君に 好き！雪！本気マジック！
A heart stained in blinding white, suki! yuki! maji magic!
大人のふりなんていいじゃん
Don't think about trying to look like an adult!
I hear that beat from town
the cute angel will come down
this is my home i 'll let you know
This is my home, I'll let you know,
namara fantastic！
namara fantastic!
the snowscape is lyrical
the street gonna be magical
the street's gonna be magical.
i 'll set you free in my land oh oh oh oh
I'll set you free in my land, oh oh oh oh!
今日の寒さも忘れるように 悩みだって悩みだって凍らせて消せる魔力よ
To forget the coldness of today, with magic to freeze all troubles
abcd ドド シシ ララ シシ マジカル ミラクル クール pop！
abcd do do shi shi la la shi shi magical miracle cool pop!
あぁ whipped した ケーキのような街は 好き！雪！本気マジック！
Ah, a town like a frosted cake, suki! yuki! maji magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは
Confetti given by the sky
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
is the angel's wings celebrating winter's festival.
light up したオーロラ色の街は 好き！雪！本気マジック！
The illuminated town of aurora, suki! yuki! maji magic!
子どもでいられたら dream land
Wish I could just be a child, dreamland.
アイツもホンモノ
Even that guy is the real deal,
とけないように ヒューヒューヒュー
hoping it won't melt, whew whew whew!
ずっとこのままじゃダメなのかな やっぱりドキドキしたいな みんな求む いつも今
Can't we stay like this forever? I still want my heart to race right now.
唱えて 1234 水金地火木 マジカル ミラクル クール pop！
Recite it! 1234, Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, magical miracle pop!
あぁホップしたウサギのような気分 好き！雪！本気マジック！
Ah, feelin' like a hopping rabbit, suki! yuki! maji magic!
あら、見えた？
Oh, could you see me?
てんさーーい！
A ge-nius!
優勝！
First place!
みんなちゅきちゅこー！
I love you all so much!
来たよ！来たよー！
You're here! You made it!
えってことで、まずね、先輩だ。あ、一人一人ちょっと名前言ってもらおうかな。
So first, senpais... Let's have each of you tell me your names.
お、あ、誰が来てくれたんですか？
Oh, who came to see me?
はーい、マリンと！
Right, Marine and...
まっすぐ燃える
Burning straight ahead—
迷うな、迷うな。あれ、迷っちゃった。やばい、えんりしちゃった。
Don't get lost. Wait, I got lost. Oh no, I panicked.
指こうじだよー！
It's Yubi Kouji!
略してきちゃったの。
You abbreviated it!
なんかすごいのおまとめりないな。
Somehow, this lacks any cohesion.
ありがとう来てくれて！
Thanks for coming!
ラミちゃんどうすんの？どうすんの？どれ何見せてみなさいよ。
What about Lamy? Show me what you've got!
ちょっとじっくり、じっくり見ていくじっくり。
Let's take a closer, careful look.
上から順番にファッションコードしていこうか。
Let's go through the fashion code from the top down.
帽子可愛いそれ。
That hat is so cute.
あそう、帽子ね、これほら。
That's right, the hat, look here.
お、お、お。
Oh, oh, oh.
おしゃれ。
Stylish!
可愛い。
Cute!
ねえ、普段からね、帽子かぶってるからね。
You know, since I usually wear a hat—
あ、そうそうそうそう。普段からね、白い帽子かぶってるから。
Ah, right, right. Because I usually wear a white hat—
これがアイドル衣装バージョンの帽子。
This is the idol costume version of the hat.
めっちゃいい！
It's so good!
じゃあちょっと下に降りて顔見ようかな。
Let's move down a bit and look at her face.
顔は、顔はどうしようね。
As for the face... what should we do?
可愛い！100万点！
So cute! A million points!
じゃあちょっとさらに下に降りようか。
Let's move down even further.
お、お、お、でかい！これね。
Oh, oh, oh, it's huge! This one.
ちょっとちょっと、ちょっとジャンプしてごらん。
Wait, wait, try jumping a bit.
なんでよ！
Why?!
え、ちょっとできないのかな？
Huh? Can I not do it?
あれ、思ったより硬いな。カチカチや。
Wait, it's stiffer than I thought. It's super stiff!
でもね、おっぱいとね、スーパー人体をね、大事にしている。さすがアイドルや！
But you know, my breasts and super body are precious. As expected of an idol!
じゃあちょっと下降りる？後ろ見たいね。
Shall we head down a bit? I want to see the back.
お、なんか後ろ側も見に行ってみたいよね。
Oh, I'd love to check out the back too.
あ、可愛い！ピンク！
Ah, cute! Pink!
リボンをピンクにしてもらいました！
I had the ribbons made pink!
めっちゃいいじゃん！
That's so good!
色もいいね、この水色もいいね。
The colors are great too, this light blue is nice.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
でね、ま、今日はちょっと、撮影会みたいなことしようかなと思うんだけど。
So today, I thought we could do something like a photo session.
ちょっとなんか、こう、人にづつなんかこうこれをし欲しいみたいなポーズがあれば、
If there are poses you'd like me to do one by one...
やろうかなと思うんだけど、なんか、ありますか？
I was thinking of doing them. Do you have any requests?
え、誰が先行く？誰が先行く？誰が先行く？
Huh, who goes first? Who goes first?
どうする？え、どうしようか。いいよ、誰ででもいいよ。
What should we do? Anything is fine, whoever's ready.
はいはいはい、じゃあ船長行きます。
Okay, okay, then Captain goes first.
いや、せっかくアイドル衣装だから、ちょっとアイドル全としたポーズを見たいわけ。
Since it's a special idol outfit, I want to see a thoroughly idol-like pose.
アイドル全としたポーズ？
A thoroughly idol-like pose?
そうね、でもポーズピタッと止まってるやつじゃなくて、ちょっと動いてからのみたいなのが見たいから。
Yeah, but instead of a rigid, static pose, I want to see one after some movement.
お！ハードルを上げるな！
Oh! Don't raise the bar!
ちょっと、軽くステップ踏んで、くるっと回って、決めみたいなのが見たい。
I'd like to see a light step, a spin, and then a final pose.
ああ、いいよ！
Ah, sure!
じゃあやっていくよ。はい、どうぞ！
Alright, here we go. Go ahead!
振り付け雑だな！
Your choreography is messy!
え、じゃあどうしようかな。いいよ、好きなステップ。
Well, what should I do? Any step is fine.
じゃあ、アイドルステップから。
Alright, starting with an idol step.
可愛い、可愛い！可愛いよ！
Cute, cute! So cute!
スクショタイム！
Screenshot time!
いや、めっちゃめちゃ可愛い！ありがとう！
Man, super, super cute! Thank you!
え、じゃあね、こうね、膝まずいて、膝まずいて、後ろ、後ろ向いて膝まずいて、後ろついて膝まずく。
Next, let's kneel down... kneel down, turn around and kneel, kneel facing backward.
え、牛こっちを振り返って、えで、あら可愛い！
Turn around this way, and... oh, cute!
可愛い、可愛い、可愛い。
Cute, cute, cute.
できるじゃんか！
You can do it!
できるじゃんか！プロデューサー！
You can do it, producer!
そうね、それカメラ上から、あいいね、いいね、あ、いいやいやいや！
Right, from above the camera... ah nice, nice!
もっと表情を見せてごらん、表情！
Show me more of your expression!
困った顔、困った顔、あ、いいですね！あら、困っちゃったね！
A troubled face... ah, nice! Oh, you look troubled!
めっちゃいいじゃん！困っちゃうの！
That's so good! Being troubled!
じゃあ次はね、ねぇちゃん、ねぇちゃんね。
Next is Nee-chan, Nee-chan.
じゃあ、艦長はね、ちょっとね、後ろから走ってきて、やっぱうちらうったら、まあね、ぼ、ぴゅ、ぴゅ、ジャンプをしてほしいなと思って。
As for the captain, run up from behind, and since it's us, I want you to do a big jump!
ぴゅるるるじゃんぷ、青春！
Pyurururu jump, youth!
フレンドだからね、一人だけちょっと一人ジャンプ。
We're friends, so just one person doing a solo jump.
いや、できや！
No, you can do it!
思いっきり飛べ、思いっきり！
Jump with all your might!
いや、可愛い！もっと、もっと！もっと上手に付けて思いっきり、いくよー！
Aw, cute! More, more! Do it better and with all your might, here we go!
しゅんだ！
Tada!
なんかみんな褒めてくれる！
Everyone's praising me!
かわいい！
So cute!
いいねー。
Nice~
なにげにこの足元の靴下もね、かわいいね、みんなさ。
And by the way, even the socks on my feet are so cute, everyone.
かわいい！
Cute!
そうなの、めっちゃかわいい！
That's right, super cute!
これあれじゃん、あの雪みかざりの柄だ！
This is, you know, that snow crystal pattern!
そうそうそうそうそう。
That's right, exactly!
今回ね、雪みかざりってないんだけど。
This time, there's no snow crystal though.
どうしたの？取れたの？
What happened? Did it come off?
あ、そう靴下に持って帰ったんだ、靴下に持って帰ったの、すいーってね。
Ah, right, I brought it to my socks, I brought it to my socks, like *swoosh*.
今回はライブ、このアイドル衣装だからちょっとシンプルめにね。
This time for the live, since it's an idol costume, keeping it a bit simple.
あのね、帽子を引き立たせるために、そう、にしました。
You know, to make the hat stand out, we did that.
え、確かにいいね、合ってる！
Ah, true, it's nice, it matches!
おいそう、みんなはどこが一番好き？
Hey right, where does everyone like best?
どこ？
Where?
えー？
Eh?
う、だみたんのお顔！
U, Damitan's face!
あ、やだ！
Ah, no way!
やだ、なにきててもかわいいよ、ありがとう。
No way, you're cute no matter what you wear, thank you.
あ、顔が！
Ah, my face!
顔が！
My face!
顔が一番、顔が！顔ね、のえちゃんは？
My face is best, my face! My face, how about Noe-chan?
え、団長はやっぱり足元の、その、ストッキングじゃなくて靴下、ソックス！
For Senchou, it's definitely the feet—not stockings, socks, socks!
いやお花の柄がめちゃめちゃかわいいなと思って。
I thought the flower pattern was super cute.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ほそしな足。
Such slender legs.
え、なんかさ、それ、のえちゃんもしかして自分の雪の柄奪っちゃったから。
Wait, did Noe-chan steal my snow pattern?
食材の、
The ingredient's...
ば、ばれちゃいました？
Did it get found out?
でもさ、そのお揃い感はあるよね、のえちゃんパイと。
But you know, there's a matching feel with Noe-chan's pair, right?
そうだね、お揃っち、お揃っち。
That's right, matching, matching.
並べたいな。
I want to line them up.
え、なんかもう一個、うちらの、3人からポーズって、
Um, like another one, poses from the three of us,
ポーズね！
Poses, right!
え、どうする？同ヨ感で、なんかみんなで、スロット、スロットに行こう、スロットね。
Um, what should we do? With the same vibe, everyone, let's go slot, slot, slot, you know.
スロット？行こうにが、顔の角度やって。
Slot? Let's go, do the facial angle.
顔の角度？えっと、のえるちゃんが、なんだっけ、上半身やって。
Facial angle? Um, Noeru-chan, what was it, do your upper body.
上半身、オッケーオッケー。
Upper body, okay okay.
が、下半身を、あ、下半身のまりね、任せろわ！
And I'll handle the lower body, leave it to me!
下半身のことなら、どこがねえの、そしたら。
Speaking of lower bodies, where can we go then?
え、待って、上から順じゃないの？こういうの、首とか首とかね、やるやつじゃん。
Wait, isn't it in order from the top? Like neck, neck, that kind of thing.
どるね、先輩から。
Doru-ne, starting from the senior.
うんとね、
Let's see,
左にちょっと傾けて？左にちょっと。
tilt a bit to the left? A bit to the left.
あ、オッケー。
Ah, okay.
え、それだけ？表情、表情の指定とか。
Eh, just that? Facial expression, specifying expression, etc.
表情？あ、じゃあ、困った顔が好きだから、困った顔がいいな。
Expression? Ah, well, I like troubled faces, so a troubled face would be nice.
照れてるような感じの、あ、いいよ！
Something like being embarrassed, ah, nice!
あららららら、女優、女優、女優良いよ！
Oh my goodness, actress, actress, good actress!
女優の顔は？
The actress face?
よし！
Alright!
女優、やっぱり団長マッスルポーズが好きだから、マッスルかな？
Actress, as expected Senchou likes the muscle pose, so maybe muscle?
うそにさ！ガション、いいいい、ガション、ちょっと待って、バランス悪いぞ！
No way! *Clang*, good good, *clang*, wait a minute, the balance is bad!
え、でも、まりね決めてくれる？
Eh, but Mari-ne, will you decide?
団長はやっぱり女の子は膝から崩れ落ちてるのがいいと思う、膝から。
Senchou thinks it's good for girls to collapse from the knees, from the knees.
はい、崩れ落ちて！
Yes, collapse!
どういうことなの？もうちょっと足開こうか。
What does that mean? Let's open our legs a bit more.
やだよう！
No way!
開いて！やだ、倒れたぞ！
Open them! Oh no, you fell over!
上半身先手だよ、これ。
The upper body is first here.
これのえ先手の先手なわ。
This is Noe-sen's absolute first.
じゃ、ちょっと下から、え、もう終わり？
Then, a bit from below, eh, it's already over?
お時間なので、あそこの、ありがとうございました！
Since it's time, over there, thank you very much!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
かわいいよ、よらみちゃん！
So cute, Yoramī-chan!
そういうことよ！
That's right!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
バイバイ、またね！
Bye-bye, see you later!
とことで皆様も、もうそろそろお時間なので、獅子の枠に行きましょう！
With that said, everyone, it's almost time, so let's head over to Shishi's stream!
ゴー！
Go!